[

](https://www.buff.game/)

Menu

[

](https://apps.apple.com/il/app/buff-game/id1556876835)

[

](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.buff.game.appmobile)

BUFF PRIVACY POLICY ("PRIVACY POLICY")
======================================

IMPORTANT: BY USING BUFF TECHNOLOGIES’ (“COMPANY” OR “WE”) PROPRIETARY SOFTWARE SOLUTION (“SERVICES”) YOU (“YOU”) ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND CONSENT THAT ALL PII (DEFINED BELOW) THAT YOU SUBMIT OR THAT IS PROCESSED OR COLLECTED THROUGH OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES WILL BE PROCESSED BY THE COMPANY AND ITS AFFILIATES IN THE MANNER AND FOR THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED IN THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY.

#### BUFF PRIVACY POLICY (“PRIVACY POLICY”)

Company is a controller of the PII it processes in relation to its customers (i.e. users of the Services), vendors, service providers or partners. YOU ARE NOT LEGALLY REQUIRED TO PROVIDE US WITH PII, HOWEVER, USE OF THE SERVICES REQUIRES THAT YOU PROVIDE PII. IF YOU CHOOSE TO WITHHOLD ANY PII REQUIRED IN RESPECT THEREOF, IT WILL NOT BE POSSIBLE FOR YOU TO USE THE SERVICES. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH HEREIN PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SERVICES. Children under the age of 18, may not access or use the Services unless they have obtained their parents’ or legal guardians’ consent, in accordance with the Buff Terms of Use located at [Terms of Use](https://www.buff.game/website-terms-of-use/). Without relieving you of your responsibility to comply with the Buff Terms of Use and the terms hereof we reserve the right (without obligation) to request additional documents so that we can verify that compliance in such respect. “PII” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person; an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier such as your IP address or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person. We recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the services, information, tools, features and functionality available on the Services offered by the Company or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies and covers how PII that the Company collects and receives, including in respect of any use of the Services, is treated. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at: [\[email protected\]](https://www.buff.game/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

* Information We Collect and How We Use It.

Summary: We collect personal data about the users of the Services. We also collect personal data included in publicly available sources. We use PII to provide and improve our Services, and to meet our contractual, ethical and legal obligations. In order to provide and operate our Services and provide services in connection therewith, we collect and process PII, including the following types of information, divided here based on the applicable lawful basis for the processing: 1(a) Processing which is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract (GDPR Article 6(1)(b)) OR Processing which is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which Company is subject (GDPR Article 6(1)(c)):

1. Your Information. When you register to use the Services we ask you to provide PII, including email address, and certain additional information when you subscribe to our Services or become an affiliate. We use this information to administer the Services, carry out our obligations, verify and carry out financial transactions, contact you for technical and administrative needs related to the Services, reply to queries and troubleshooting, detect and prevent fraud, compliance and audit purposes, of identity theft and more.

1(b) Processing which is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Company or by a third party (GDPR Article 6(1)(f)) of providing efficient and effective Services to our customers, or displaying ads, including:

1. Usage Information. When you use the Services, we automatically receive and record information from your browser, including without limitation information and statistics about your online/offline status, your IP address, geolocation data (including country and city), browser identifiers, internet service provider, type of browser, your regional and language settings and software and hardware attributes. Our systems automatically record and store technical information regarding the method and nature of your use of the Services. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your browser on a network, or in this case, the Internet. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. The Company uses all of the PII identified in this Section in order to understand the usage trends and preferences of our users, including recent visits to our Services and how you move around different sections of our Services for analytics purposes and in order to make our Services more intuitive.
2. User Communications. When you send emails or other communications to the Company, we retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our Services. We will send you newsletters and promotional communications, you may opt-out of the list at any time by submitting a request at the following [link](https://url3841.buff.game/wf/unsubscribe?upn=F4-2FOF9z7OAUXLsih0vOzh-2FFQvHgYSdwcbo7NfczBRtLF6RWx-2F1JdSlYWCrdrG-2Bl0uOEp69wKfrxf1SX2yYjCOai9IMt9-2B-2BskKnc872TW2vbEE-2Fz-2FFnxY10ByGjk7fLpg-2FBR-2FKvglecdQeo-2BrGca8PfEHzzRRejKm-2FdZHbl5mjfHKFpjHT97n00x0NwYlhnXme4TUfxxRUbC8uMpidT1gRao3plmZFFTKbezEt9wfInTpjacZbQcBH6pBmsiQmPk5Z4XM2jtXc-2BSURtZ9zeo0RJooh0EfRO8Zx0am-2F2ZGym6YUzpNDQ6y82X6UTI9QZc8atog8ZJJEwfagEWaiMCyBFV-2BXUgFdnysoM1XvQIvJB8zc-2Fj-2B6iScKlhZQM-2BxIMmmAOcvZ01xE0nrmUFN7zTWlA-3D-3D).
3. Physical Prizes. When you take part in our community challenges you may be required to provide us with a valid shipping address to receive physical prizes.
4. Aggregate and Analytical Data. In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the customers of the Services, we may conduct research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the PII and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and we may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, suppliers and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes. We also use aggregate data for monetization.
5. Cookies. When you use our website we use cookies. See ‘Cookies’ section below for more details

* Cookies.

Summary: We use cookies, pixels and similar technologies on our Services. You can disable cookies but then your online experience on our Services may be limited. In order to collect the data described herein we use temporary cookies that remain on your browser for a limited period of time. We also use persistent cookies that remain on your browser/device until the Company’s Services are removed, in order to manage and maintain the Services and record your use of the Services. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user. A cookie is a small piece of information which is sent to and stored on your browser. Cookies do not damage your browser/device. Most browsers/devices allow you to block cookies but you may not be able to use some features on the Services if you block them. You may set most browsers/devices to notify you if you receive a cookie (this enables you to decide if you want to accept it or not). We also use web beacons via the Services to collect information. Web beacons or “gifs”, are electronic images that are used in our Services or in our emails. We use Web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

* Personalized and Interest Based Ads. Our Services may in the future include interest based ads, which means advertisements we believe that may be valuable to you, based on the PII provided to us. Such ads may be placed by us or our third party affiliates and service providers.

* Links. Links to other services, sites and applications are provided by the Company as a convenience to our users. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other sites and applications and you visit them at your own risk. This Privacy Policy applies solely to PII collected by us.

* No Unauthorized Minor Data. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 18 has provided us with their PII without their parents or legal guardians’ consent, please contact us at the address given above and we will endeavor to delete that PII from our databases.

* Information Sharing.

Summary: We transfer your PII to third parties who assist us in providing the Services. We have a contract with those third parties to govern their processing on our behalf. We may also transfer PII to comply with any obligations by which we are bound or to an investor or in connection with a merger or acquisition or similar transaction. As part of providing the Services our affiliates, agents, representatives and service providers will have access to your PII. We require these parties to process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy and subject to security and other appropriate confidentiality safeguards.  The Company will also share PII in the following circumstances: (a) as required for providing the Services; (b) for maintenance and improvement of the Services; (c) if we become involved in a reorganization, merger, consolidation, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of our assets, with any type of entity, whether public, private, foreign or local; and/or (d) to satisfy applicable law or prevention of fraud or harm or to enforce applicable agreements and/or their terms, including investigation of potential violations thereof. We periodically add and remove third party providers. At present our third-party providers to whom we may transfer PII include also the following:

* Cloud computing providers, such as AWS;
* Business partners. such as Overwolf;
* Data security, data backup, and data access control systems;
* Our lawyers, accountants, and other standard business software and partners.

* Data Security. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of PII. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

* Data Retention.

Summary: We retain PII only for as long as necessary to meet our contractual, legal and ethical obligations, which for different types of PII will be different periods.

1. Company will retain PII in accordance with its record retention policy. PII associated with the users of the Services will be retained only for as long as required for the Services, or until requested to be deleted. Company performs periodic reviews of our databases, and have established specific time limits for data retention, based on the criticality of th
2. e PII and the purposes of the data processing. We will also retain PII to meet any audit, compliance and business best-practices.
3. Personal Data that is no longer retained will be anonymized or deleted. Non-personal, non-identifiable, metadata and statistical information concerning the use of our Services are retained by Company indefinitely. Some PII may also be retained on our third-party service providers’ servers until deleted in accordance with their privacy policy and their retention policy.

* Data Integrity. The Company processes PII only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service agreements. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the PII we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their PII whenever necessary. Nothing in this Privacy Policy is interpreted as an obligation to store information, and we may, at our own discretion, delete or avoid from recording and storing any and all information.

* Rights of Data Subjects.

1. Right of Access and Rectification. Data subjects have the right to know what PII we collect about them and to ensure that such data is accurate and relevant for the purposes for which we collected it; that information is made available here in this policy. We allow data subjects the option to access and obtain a copy of their PII and to rectify such PII if it is not accurate, complete or updated.
2. Right to Delete PII or Restrict Processing. Data subjects have the right to delete their PII or restrict its processing. We may postpone or deny such requests if the PII is in current use for the purposes for which it was collected or for other legitimate purposes such as compliance with legal obligations.
3. Right to Withdraw Consent. Data subjects have the right to withdraw their consent to the processing of their PII, where the processing is based on consent. Exercising this right will not affect the lawfulness of processing the PII based on consent obtained before its withdrawal, or processing based on other legal bases.
4. Right of Data Portability. Where technically feasible, data subjects have the right to ask to transfer their PII in accordance with their right to data portability, if required pursuant to applicable law.

Data subjects may exercise the above rights by sending a request to [\[email protected\]](https://www.buff.game/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

1. Right to Lodge Complaint. Data subjects also have the right to lodge a complaint with a data protection supervisory authority regarding the processing of their PII.

Note that we may have to undertake a process to identify a Data Subject exercising their rights, and we will keep details of such rights exercised for our compliance and audit requirements. PII may be either deleted or retained in an aggregated manner without being linked to any identifiers or Personal Data, depending on technical commercial capability. Such information may continue to be used by Company

* Enforcement. The Company regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our treatment of PII by contacting us as provided above. When we receive formal written complaints, it is the Company’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of PII that cannot be resolved between the Company and an individual.

* Changes to This Privacy Policy. The Company may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of this Privacy Policy will be available at: https://buff.game/buff-privacy-policy. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Data Updated” date and your continued use of our services will constitute your active acceptance of the changes to and terms of the Privacy Policy.

* International transfer of personal data. The server on which the Services are hosted and/or through which the Services are processed may be outside the country from which you access the Services and may be outside your country of residence. Some of the uses and disclosures mentioned in this Privacy Policy involve the transfer of your PII to various countries around the world that may have different levels of privacy protection than your country and will be transferred outside of the European Economic Area. If there is a transfer of your PII outside the EEA we will, in the absence of an EC Adequacy decision relevant to the destination country or to the transfer, seek to rely on appropriate safeguards such as entering into appropriate EC approved standard contractual clauses (see [https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/international-transfers/transfer/index\_en.htm](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/international-transfers/transfer/index_en.htm)). By submitting your PII through the Services, you  acknowledge, and agree that we will collect, use, transfer, and disclose your PII as described in this Privacy Policy.

* Questions. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about the way we process your PII, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.buff.game/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). If you wish to delete all information regarding your use of the Services, please contact us at: [\[email protected\]](https://www.buff.game/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Do Not Track Notices. You are also advised that Company does not respond to “Do Not Track” signals. You can manage your cookie settings [here](#). Last Date Updated: December 20, 2021.

[

](https://discord.com/invite/fAhV4SY)[

](https://l.linklyhq.com/l/1guEn)[

](https://l.linklyhq.com/l/1gu4Q)[

](https://www.facebook.com/buff.game)[

](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCzVXqxjcAjSHTxABpHngnPQ)[

](https://l.linklyhq.com/l/1guG8)

###### Menu

###### Earn For Playing Games

###### FAQ

###### DISCLAIMER

BUFF.GAME isn’t endorsed by Riot Games and doesn’t reflect the views or opinions of Riot Games or anyone officially involved in producing or managing League of Legends and or Valorant. League of Legends, Valorant and Riot Games are trademarks or registered trademarks of Riot Games, Inc. League of Legends, Valorant © Riot Games, Inc.

[Manage consent](javascript:void(0))

© 2024 Buff. All Rights Reserved.  

Don't Miss This Special Offer:
------------------------------

Triple Welcome Bonus 90 Buff Points Instead of 30

Time Left:

H

M

S

We and our {{count}} partners use cookies and other tracking technologies to improve your experience on our website. We may store and/or access information on a device and process personal data, such as your IP address and browsing data, for personalised advertising and content, advertising and content measurement, audience research and services development. Additionally, we may utilize precise geolocation data and identification through device scanning.

Please note that your consent will be valid across all our subdomains. You can change or withdraw your consent at any time by clicking the “Consent Preferences” button at the bottom of your screen. We respect your choices and are committed to providing you with a transparent and secure browsing experience.

Cookie SettingsReject AllAccept All

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

Customize your consent preferences for Cookie Categories and advertising tracking preferences for Purposes & Features and Vendors below. You can give granular consent for each Third Party Vendor and Google Ad Tech Provider. Most vendors require explicit consent for personal data processing, while some rely on legitimate interest. However, you have the right to object to their use of legitimate interest.

Cookie Categories Purposes & Features Vendors

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| AWSALBCORS | 7 days | This cookie is managed by Amazon Web Services and is used for load balancing. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-advertisement | 1 year | Set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin, this cookie is used to record the user consent for the cookies in the "Advertisement" category . |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| elementor | never | This cookie is used by the website's WordPress theme. It allows the website owner to implement or change the website's content in real-time. |
| trustedsite\_visit | 1 day | This cookie is set by the provider McAfee for website security. This cookie is used for storing the number of visits. |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

Performance

 performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

Analytics

 analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_ga | 2 years | The \_ga cookie, installed by Google Analytics, calculates visitor, session and campaign data and also keeps track of site usage for the site's analytics report. The cookie stores information anonymously and assigns a randomly generated number to recognize unique visitors. |
| \_gat\_UA-114852827-1 | 1 minute | This is a pattern type cookie set by Google Analytics, where the pattern element on the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. It appears to be a variation of the \_gat cookie which is used to limit the amount of data recorded by Google on high traffic volume websites. |
| \_gcl\_au | 3 months | Provided by Google Tag Manager to experiment advertisement efficiency of websites using their services. |
| \_gid | 1 day | Installed by Google Analytics, \_gid cookie stores information on how visitors use a website, while also creating an analytics report of the website's performance. Some of the data that are collected include the number of visitors, their source, and the pages they visit anonymously. |
| \_uetsid | 1 day | This cookies are used to collect analytical information about how visitors use the website. This information is used to compile report and improve site. |
| CONSENT | 16 years 3 months 17 days 13 hours | These cookies are set via embedded youtube-videos. They register anonymous statistical data on for example how many times the video is displayed and what settings are used for playback.No sensitive data is collected unless you log in to your google account, in that case your choices are linked with your account, for example if you click “like” on a video. |

Advertisement

 advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_fbp | 3 months | This cookie is set by Facebook to display advertisements when either on Facebook or on a digital platform powered by Facebook advertising, after visiting the website. |
| anj | 3 months | No description available. |
| fr  | 3 months | Facebook sets this cookie to show relevant advertisements to users by tracking user behaviour across the web, on sites that have Facebook pixel or Facebook social plugin. |
| IDE | 1 year 24 days | Google DoubleClick IDE cookies are used to store information about how the user uses the website to present them with relevant ads and according to the user profile. |
| MUID | 1 year 24 days | Bing sets this cookie to recognize unique web browsers visiting Microsoft sites. This cookie is used for advertising, site analytics, and other operations. |
| test\_cookie | 15 minutes | The test\_cookie is set by doubleclick.net and is used to determine if the user's browser supports cookies. |
| uuid2 | 3 months | The uuid2 cookie is set by AppNexus and records information that helps in differentiating between devices and browsers. This information is used to pick out ads delivered by the platform and assess the ad performance and its attribute payment. |
| VISITOR\_INFO1\_LIVE | 5 months 27 days | A cookie set by YouTube to measure bandwidth that determines whether the user gets the new or old player interface. |
| YSC | session | YSC cookie is set by Youtube and is used to track the views of embedded videos on Youtube pages. |
| yt-remote-connected-devices | never | YouTube sets this cookie to store the video preferences of the user using embedded YouTube video. |
| yt-remote-device-id | never | YouTube sets this cookie to store the video preferences of the user using embedded YouTube video. |
| yt.innertube::nextId | never | These cookies are set via embedded youtube-videos. |
| yt.innertube::requests | never | These cookies are set via embedded youtube-videos. |

Others

 others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_rdt\_uuid | 3 months | No description available. |
| \_uetvid | 1 year 24 days | No description available. |
| AWSALB | 7 days | AWSALB is a cookie generated by the Application load balancer in the Amazon Web Services. It works slightly different from AWSELB. |
| buff-908 | 10 years | No description |
| outbrain\_cid\_fetch | 5 minutes | No description available. |
| trustedsite\_tm\_float\_seen | 5 minutes | No description available. |

Purposes

 purpose

Store and/or access information on a device

 1

Cookies, device or similar online identifiers (e.g. login-based identifiers, randomly assigned identifiers, network based identifiers) together with other information (e.g. browser type and information, language, screen size, supported technologies etc.) can be stored or read on your device to recognise it each time it connects to an app or to a website, for one or several of the purposes presented here.

Illustrations

* Most purposes explained in this notice rely on the storage or accessing of information from your device when you use an app or visit a website. For example, a vendor or publisher might need to store a cookie on your device during your first visit on a website, to be able to recognise your device during your next visits (by accessing this cookie each time).

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Use limited data to select advertising

 2

 2

Advertising presented to you on this service can be based on limited data, such as the website or app you are using, your non-precise location, your device type or which content you are (or have been) interacting with (for example, to limit the number of times an ad is presented to you).

Illustrations

* A car manufacturer wants to promote its electric vehicles to environmentally conscious users living in the city after office hours. The advertising is presented on a page with related content (such as an article on climate change actions) after 6:30 p.m. to users whose non-precise location suggests that they are in an urban zone.
* A large producer of watercolour paints wants to carry out an online advertising campaign for its latest watercolour range, diversifying its audience to reach as many amateur and professional artists as possible and avoiding showing the ad next to mismatched content (for instance, articles about how to paint your house). The number of times that the ad has been presented to you is detected and limited, to avoid presenting it too often.

Number of Vendors seeking consent or relying on legitimate interest:

Create profiles for personalised advertising

 3

Information about your activity on this service (such as forms you submit, content you look at) can be stored and combined with other information about you (for example, information from your previous activity on this service and other websites or apps) or similar users. This is then used to build or improve a profile about you (that might include possible interests and personal aspects). Your profile can be used (also later) to present advertising that appears more relevant based on your possible interests by this and other entities.

Illustrations

* If you read several articles about the best bike accessories to buy, this information could be used to create a profile about your interest in bike accessories. Such a profile may be used or improved later on, on the same or a different website or app to present you with advertising for a particular bike accessory brand. If you also look at a configurator for a vehicle on a luxury car manufacturer website, this information could be combined with your interest in bikes to refine your profile and make an assumption that you are interested in luxury cycling gear.
* An apparel company wishes to promote its new line of high-end baby clothes. It gets in touch with an agency that has a network of clients with high income customers (such as high-end supermarkets) and asks the agency to create profiles of young parents or couples who can be assumed to be wealthy and to have a new child, so that these can later be used to present advertising within partner apps based on those profiles.

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Use profiles to select personalised advertising

 4

Advertising presented to you on this service can be based on your advertising profiles, which can reflect your activity on this service or other websites or apps (like the forms you submit, content you look at), possible interests and personal aspects.

Illustrations

* An online retailer wants to advertise a limited sale on running shoes. It wants to target advertising to users who previously looked at running shoes on its mobile app. Tracking technologies might be used to recognise that you have previously used the mobile app to consult running shoes, in order to present you with the corresponding advertisement on the app.
* A profile created for personalised advertising in relation to a person having searched for bike accessories on a website can be used to present the relevant advertisement for bike accessories on a mobile app of another organisation.

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Create profiles to personalise content

 5

Information about your activity on this service (for instance, forms you submit, non-advertising content you look at) can be stored and combined with other information about you (such as your previous activity on this service or other websites or apps) or similar users. This is then used to build or improve a profile about you (which might for example include possible interests and personal aspects). Your profile can be used (also later) to present content that appears more relevant based on your possible interests, such as by adapting the order in which content is shown to you, so that it is even easier for you to find content that matches your interests.

Illustrations

* You read several articles on how to build a treehouse on a social media platform. This information might be added to a profile to mark your interest in content related to outdoors as well as do-it-yourself guides (with the objective of allowing the personalisation of content, so that for example you are presented with more blog posts and articles on treehouses and wood cabins in the future).
* You have viewed three videos on space exploration across different TV apps. An unrelated news platform with which you have had no contact builds a profile based on that viewing behaviour, marking space exploration as a topic of possible interest for other videos.

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Use profiles to select personalised content

 6

Content presented to you on this service can be based on your content personalisation profiles, which can reflect your activity on this or other services (for instance, the forms you submit, content you look at), possible interests and personal aspects. This can for example be used to adapt the order in which content is shown to you, so that it is even easier for you to find (non-advertising) content that matches your interests.

Illustrations

* You read articles on vegetarian food on a social media platform and then use the cooking app of an unrelated company. The profile built about you on the social media platform will be used to present you vegetarian recipes on the welcome screen of the cooking app.
* You have viewed three videos about rowing across different websites. An unrelated video sharing platform will recommend five other videos on rowing that may be of interest to you when you use your TV app, based on a profile built about you when you visited those different websites to watch online videos.

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Measure advertising performance

 7

 7

Information regarding which advertising is presented to you and how you interact with it can be used to determine how well an advert has worked for you or other users and whether the goals of the advertising were reached. For instance, whether you saw an ad, whether you clicked on it, whether it led you to buy a product or visit a website, etc. This is very helpful to understand the relevance of advertising campaigns.

Illustrations

* You have clicked on an advertisement about a “black Friday” discount by an online shop on the website of a publisher and purchased a product. Your click will be linked to this purchase. Your interaction and that of other users will be measured to know how many clicks on the ad led to a purchase.
* You are one of very few to have clicked on an advertisement about an “international appreciation day” discount by an online gift shop within the app of a publisher. The publisher wants to have reports to understand how often a specific ad placement within the app, and notably the “international appreciation day” ad, has been viewed or clicked by you and other users, in order to help the publisher and its partners (such as agencies) optimise ad placements.

Number of Vendors seeking consent or relying on legitimate interest:

Measure content performance

 8

 8

Information regarding which content is presented to you and how you interact with it can be used to determine whether the (non-advertising) content e.g. reached its intended audience and matched your interests. For instance, whether you read an article, watch a video, listen to a podcast or look at a product description, how long you spent on this service and the web pages you visit etc. This is very helpful to understand the relevance of (non-advertising) content that is shown to you.

Illustrations

* You have read a blog post about hiking on a mobile app of a publisher and followed a link to a recommended and related post. Your interactions will be recorded as showing that the initial hiking post was useful to you and that it was successful in interesting you in the related post. This will be measured to know whether to produce more posts on hiking in the future and where to place them on the home screen of the mobile app.
* You were presented a video on fashion trends, but you and several other users stopped watching after 30 seconds. This information is then used to evaluate the right length of future videos on fashion trends.

Number of Vendors seeking consent or relying on legitimate interest:

Understand audiences through statistics or combinations of data from different sources

 9

 9

Reports can be generated based on the combination of data sets (like user profiles, statistics, market research, analytics data) regarding your interactions and those of other users with advertising or (non-advertising) content to identify common characteristics (for instance, to determine which target audiences are more receptive to an ad campaign or to certain contents).

Illustrations

* The owner of an online bookstore wants commercial reporting showing the proportion of visitors who consulted and left its site without buying, or consulted and bought the last celebrity autobiography of the month, as well as the average age and the male/female distribution of each category. Data relating to your navigation on its site and to your personal characteristics is then used and combined with other such data to produce these statistics.
* An advertiser wants to better understand the type of audience interacting with its adverts. It calls upon a research institute to compare the characteristics of users who interacted with the ad with typical attributes of users of similar platforms, across different devices. This comparison reveals to the advertiser that its ad audience is mainly accessing the adverts through mobile devices and is likely in the 45-60 age range.

Number of Vendors seeking consent or relying on legitimate interest:

Develop and improve services

 10

 10

Information about your activity on this service, such as your interaction with ads or content, can be very helpful to improve products and services and to build new products and services based on user interactions, the type of audience, etc. This specific purpose does not include the development or improvement of user profiles and identifiers.

Illustrations

* A technology platform working with a social media provider notices a growth in mobile app users, and sees based on their profiles that many of them are connecting through mobile connections. It uses a new technology to deliver ads that are formatted for mobile devices and that are low-bandwidth, to improve their performance.
* An advertiser is looking for a way to display ads on a new type of consumer device. It collects information regarding the way users interact with this new kind of device to determine whether it can build a new mechanism for displaying advertising on this type of device.

Number of Vendors seeking consent or relying on legitimate interest:

Use limited data to select content

 11

 11

Content presented to you on this service can be based on limited data, such as the website or app you are using, your non-precise location, your device type, or which content you are (or have been) interacting with (for example, to limit the number of times a video or an article is presented to you).

Illustrations

* A travel magazine has published an article on its website about the new online courses proposed by a language school, to improve travelling experiences abroad. The school’s blog posts are inserted directly at the bottom of the page, and selected on the basis of your non-precise location (for instance, blog posts explaining the course curriculum for different languages than the language of the country you are situated in).
* A sports news mobile app has started a new section of articles covering the most recent football games. Each article includes videos hosted by a separate streaming platform showcasing the highlights of each match. If you fast-forward a video, this information may be used to select a shorter video to play next.

Number of Vendors seeking consent or relying on legitimate interest:

Special purposes

Ensure security, prevent and detect fraud, and fix errors

Your data can be used to monitor for and prevent unusual and possibly fraudulent activity (for example, regarding advertising, ad clicks by bots), and ensure systems and processes work properly and securely. It can also be used to correct any problems you, the publisher or the advertiser may encounter in the delivery of content and ads and in your interaction with them.

Illustrations

* An advertising intermediary delivers ads from various advertisers to its network of partnering websites. It notices a large increase in clicks on ads relating to one advertiser, and uses data regarding the source of the clicks to determine that 80% of the clicks come from bots rather than humans.

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Deliver and present advertising and content

Certain information (like an IP address or device capabilities) is used to ensure the technical compatibility of the content or advertising, and to facilitate the transmission of the content or ad to your device.

Illustrations

* Clicking on a link in an article might normally send you to another page or part of the article. To achieve this, 1°) your browser sends a request to a server linked to the website, 2°) the server answers back (“here is the article you asked for”), using technical information automatically included in the request sent by your device, to properly display the information / images that are part of the article you asked for. Technically, such exchange of information is necessary to deliver the content that appears on your screen.

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Save and communicate privacy choices

The choices you make regarding the purposes and entities listed in this notice are saved and made available to those entities in the form of digital signals (such as a string of characters). This is necessary in order to enable both this service and those entities to respect such choices.

Illustrations

* When you visit a website and are offered a choice between consenting to the use of profiles for personalised advertising or not consenting, the choice you make is saved and made available to advertising providers, so that advertising presented to you respects that choice.

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Features

Match and combine data from other data sources

Information about your activity on this service may be matched and combined with other information relating to you and originating from various sources (for instance your activity on a separate online service, your use of a loyalty card in-store, or your answers to a survey), in support of the purposes explained in this notice.

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Link different devices

In support of the purposes explained in this notice, your device might be considered as likely linked to other devices that belong to you or your household (for instance because you are logged in to the same service on both your phone and your computer, or because you may use the same Internet connection on both devices).

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Identify devices based on information transmitted automatically

Your device might be distinguished from other devices based on information it automatically sends when accessing the Internet (for instance, the IP address of your Internet connection or the type of browser you are using) in support of the purposes exposed in this notice.

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Special Features

 specialfeature

Use precise geolocation data

 1

With your acceptance, your precise location (within a radius of less than 500 metres) may be used in support of the purposes explained in this notice.

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Actively scan device characteristics for identification

 2

With your acceptance, certain characteristics specific to your device might be requested and used to distinguish it from other devices (such as the installed fonts or plugins, the resolution of your screen) in support of the purposes explained in this notice.

Number of Vendors seeking consent:

Third Party Vendors

 vendors

Google Ad Tech Providers

 google-vendors

Reject All Save My Preferences Accept All
